thepositivemom.com 2017-11-20

# The Positive MOM Privacy Policy ★ Elayna Fernandez ~ The Positive MOM ♥

[ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") values your interest, willingness and trust in our services.  We vow to serve you at the best of our ability, and this includes our commitment to safeguard your privacy and security while doing business with us.

Collecting information makes it possible for [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") to deliver the kind of service you expect. At [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger "), you will be asked to share your identifiable information for various purposes, including:

**1-     **To request products and services  
**2-     **To request information  
**3-     **To sign up for updates  
**4-     **To provide feedback  on our products and services

Upon voluntary form submission, your IP Address is recorded. Your visit details are traced for statistical purposes. In addition, content that is transmitted through e-mail correspondence is retained in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.

ElaynaFernandez.com is not directed toward minors. [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") does not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children.

You will never be asked for sensitive information while filling out a form at [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ").

The information collected is used to:  
**1-     **Provide customers products and services requested  
**2-     **Respond to your inquiries  
**3-     **Personalize your experience  
**4-     **Supply information about and promote our services  
**5-     **Resolve problems actively and proactively

Personal or business information provided via [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") is transmitted securely, considered strictly confidential, and will NOT be shared, disclosed, or sold to any third party without your express consent to such action.

Please be warned that when you click on a link that takes you to another Web site, any and all information you provide, is subject to the privacy policy of that site. [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") does not control and is not responsible for the practices of such sites.

By visiting or using [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger "), you agree to the provisions of this Privacy Promise.  If you are not in agreement with the provisions of this Privacy Policy, please refrain from using [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ").

If you require further information or have questions with regard to the [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ")[.](http://www.designed2impress.com/) privacy policy, you may send your inquiry to Elayna Fernandez:

**By E-mail:** | elayna@thepositivemom.com  
---|---  
**By mail:** | P.O. Box 162223, Fort Worth, TX 76131  
  
[ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") reserves the right to amend this Privacy Promise at any time, for any reason and, without notice. Any amendments will be effective when posted on the appropriate websites. This policy is effective as of January 1, 2009 and supersedes any and all privacy practices posted prior to that date.

This Privacy Policy is governed by the laws of the State of Florida. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") BE LIABLE FOR ANY SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM THE USE OF THE INFORMATION OR MATERIALS ON THIS SITE, EVEN IF [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") OR AN AUTHORIZED REPRESENTATIVE OF [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

Thank you for visiting and using [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ")!

**Special Note About Reviews/Giveaways**

[ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") is the writer and distributor of posts, reviews, giveaways, deals and any other material presented {unless otherwise indicated}. 100% of the opinions and writings are [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ")‘s and can not be duplicated without prior permission. Images and links were used with permission from the website/ promoters discussed.

[ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") is not responsible for the delivery of the winners prizes.  All complaints and dissatisfactions with the website or products within are to be discussed with the sponsoring company.

Giveaway winners are chosen by a random generator and failure to follow the rules of entry disqualifies that entry. By entering this giveaway, you understand and agree that [ThePositiveMOM.com](http://thepositivemom.com/ "The Positive MOM - Elayna Fernandez - mommy blogger ") is is no way responsible for the production, delivery, or quality of the received product.

© Elayna Fernández ~ The Positive MOM
